https://www.seasiainfotech.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
Privacy and data protection principles followed by Seasia Infotech
This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 2019
This privacy policy page covers how Seasia Infotech (“seasiainfotech.com, "we", “us”, and “our”) use, share, collect, dispose and retrieve (collectively "processes") your personal information. Personal information being any sort of information which could recognize you, or can be associated with you.
Along with this privacy policy page, we've strived to be as translucent as possible concerning our data collection and management process. Your right regarding your private data is also included in later parts.
This privacy policy pertains to the data which we collect through our site, products, services, and by offline reach outs through messages, emails, and calls. These means will be collectively termed as “services” from hither on.
With “You”, we're addressing our customers, sales prospects, service users, or people whose information is there on our servers.
Data Retention
We keep your information for as long as we require it and if we ever feel that it is no longer needed for us to keep your data, we may dispose all of it in a secure manner.
If any user ever wants to get forgotten from our records, they can be at any time. For that, they just need to contact us and we'll happily assist them with their needs.
Security
Securing the personal information of every single individual is the highest and the most important priority of our data retention practices. Analytical and Customer relationship management software which we're using are utilized and trusted by many well-reputed companies.
We also have a regular check on vulnerabilities (time to time) to bypass any security and data leakage problems thereof.
If you've any query ongoing in your mind in regard to data security and retention of your information, reach out to us anytime. We assure to provide you with the right solution.
Cookies and Web Beacons
“Cookie” is a small file having a code which site or service has on the browser whenever you use it. This cookie file is used to know you whenever you use that website or service.
Seasia Infotech uses first and third party cookies to save your time and optimize the users' experience.
Aside from user preference, cookies help us know the browsing pattern of yours on seasiainfotech.com and let us know parts of our site which are most commonly utilized. Further, it also helps us know other information like browser and device information, the geographical location of our user, their IP address, their referring sites, etc. for logical purpose.
These cookies are an indispensable part of our site and necessary for it to function as expected. In a case of any doubt, you can question us about our cookie policy by reaching out us to sales@seasiainfotech.com
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies to users who visit our website while carrying out online activities in Seasia Infotech. This policy is not applicable to any data gathered offline or via other modes other than this site.
Children's Information
Our other top priority is the protection of children while they are using the Internet. At Seasia Infotech, we urge guardians and parents to have a cross-check over the activities their children are performing while carrying out an online activity.
Seasia Infotech never asks for any personal identifiable information from children who are below the age of 13 years. However, if you think there's something alike this happened with your children then we urge you to directly contact with us so that we can have a look into it.
Contact Us
If anything mentioned in this privacy policy seems confusing or less clear,
please feel free to reach out by writing to sales@seasiainfotech.com, any kind of question or doubt concerned to our privacy policies are welcome.
